=Reincarnated Love=
=Episode 7=
His Majesty will visit here
in disguise tomorrow.
Inspect every alley and main road.
Don't allow the slightest mistake.
Yes.
Shitou,
take your men and secure East Street.
The rest guard the West Market.
- Move!
- Yes!
Come with me.
(On a bitterly cold night,)
(she's at such an old age.)
Here.
Let me.
Huo Linchuan, be careful!
Ruoli.
Troublesome.
Mr. Huo, are you hurt?
I'm fine.
Take her away.
- Are you okay?
It's so late already.
Why are you here?
I just had a dream.
You were slain by a woman in it.
I woke up and couldn't find you.
So, I came out searching for you.
You risked your life
to save me just now.
Didn't you fear for your safety?
The pact has been made.
I'll give my all to honor my promise.
Would you rather have me do nothing
when I know you're in danger?
Was it only for the pact,
or have you
come to care for me just a little?
I...
ظآزWhere shall I seekظآز
ظآزThe traces of your past livesظآز
ظآزI'd spend a lifetime's luck
just for youظآز
Jiang Ruoli,
from now on,
I seek more than just an ally.
ظآزDreams lift the night
where stars grow thinظآز
ظآزWhen shall I meet you again
in another lifeظآز
ظآزThe galaxy stirs;
destiny endlessly returnsظآز
ظآزIf I could, let me guard you this timeظآز
ظآزHow did this feeling beginظآز
ظآزIn each trial, longing deepensظآز
Jiang Ruoli,
from now on,
ظآزWhen the night fades,
the moon shines longerظآز
I seek more than just an ally.
ظآزA fleeting dream
shines through the rainظآز
ظآزThrough three lifetimes,
we never partظآز
ظآزA thousand years of snow
fall into your palmظآز
ظآزHow does love fade awayظآز
ظآزEach thought recalls the pastظآز
ظآزLonging burns into a lasting acheظآز
ظآزFrost stains the white robesظآز
ظآزMist and clouds veil the skyظآز
(9th lifetime,
Stabbed to death by Ruoli)
The pact has been made.
I'll give my all to honor my promise.
Would you rather have me do nothing
when I know you're in danger?
(Stabbed to death)
(Stabbed to death by Ruoli)
Milady,
don't be afraid.
I am here.
Last night,
I took his fatal blow in his stead.
Yet this piercing heartache
still haunts my dreams.
Too great a fright
often brings on nightmares.
You'll recover once you calm down.
Mr. Huo is occupied with duties.
He left at the Yin hour.
But before leaving, he told me
to watch over you by the bed.
Mind your tongue.
Who asked you?
Why haven't I seen Ruyan?
The storm was wild last night.
She might've been
held up with her beloved.
A young maid like you
shouldn't say such things.
I was wrong.
When she returns,
call her to see me.
We can't delay her marriage any longer.
Sure.
He left at the Yin hour.
Why is he still not back?
Jiang Ruoli,
die!
(Huo Mansion)
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
Ruyan?
No.
She's Ruyan's twin sister,
Ruyi.
(The one who tried to kill me
in my dream)
(was Ruyi.)
Jiang Ruoli,
you heartless woman!
Return my sister's life!
What did she ever do wrong?
Why did you drive her to death?
Miss, calm down.
What did you say?
What happened to Ruyan?
The farewell letter?
(Ruyi,)
(by the time you read this,
I'd be dead.)
(This is of grave consequence.)
(Ruyan)
(Please don't blame my lady.)
If I'd arrived a step later today,
the outcome would've been unthinkable.
It was all because I was careless
and failed to notice in time.
Regarding Ruyan,
you shouldn't worry too much.
There may be a misunderstanding.
Ruyan is like a sister to me.
After hearing what Ruyi said,
how could I not be concerned?
If something truly happened to Ruyan,
I...
If you ever need anything,
just say the word.
I'll do all I can.
Earlier, Mr. Lu
had his arm around Mrs. Huo's waist,
his jade belt hook brushing
against her gown's folds.
No wonder Mr. Huo neglects his wife.
Mr. Lu claimed this place first.
- Mr. Huo.
Get lost.
ظآزThe dream shatteredظآز
ظآزLike illusion, yet trueظآز
ظآزLike a restless soulظآز
ظآزHow vagueظآز
ظآزRain and blood, drifting wildظآز
ظآزA blade of frost in dreamsظآز
ظآزLove and hate entwinedظآز
ظآزRise and fall, yet never fadeظآز
ظآزHow can I turn the tides
of this fleeting lifeظآز
ظآزWhen fate falls apartظآز
ظآزMemories return,
carving tears upon my faceظآز
ظآزYet I can't hold onظآز
ظآزOnly warmth remains
where longing once burnedظآز
ظآزLife after lifeظآز
ظآزFated to meet, but never meant to beظآز
ظآزStill, I refuse to bow or yieldظآز
ظآزIn this life, love becomes my bladeظآز
ظآزTo break free from reincarnationظآز
ظآزAll past affairs tangled with regretظآز
ظآزNow shatter apartظآز
ظآزBy fate and karmic ties confinedظآز
ظآزIs this fate or calamityظآز
ظآزIs it life, death, or parting painظآز
ظآزI ask only for a moment of peace,
as devout as my heartظآز
ظآزIn the next life, grant me one kissظآز
ظآزTo kiss the snow upon the brows,
and the depths of your gazeظآز
ظآزFor once we kissed,
destiny bound us to never partظآز
ظآزThis fleeting life feels but a dreamظآز
ظآزSober or indulgeظآز
ظآزI only wish to be with you,
with all my heartظآز